http://www.dolphinics.com/company/privacy_policy.html

("us", "we", or "our") operates http://www.dolphinics.com
(the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
We are a Data Controller of your information.
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information
described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we
collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:
We
needs to perform a contract with you
You have given us permission to do so
Processing your personal information is in our legitimate interests
We needs to comply with the law
We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site and our business. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name ("Personal Information").
Log Data
Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site ("Log Data").
This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information.
We will retain your personal information only for as long
as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will
retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with
our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.
If
you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have
certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal
Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our
systems, please contact us.
In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.
The right of rectification.
The right to object.
The right of restriction.
The right to data portability
The right to withdraw consent
Communications
We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer's hard drive.
Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of (December 17th 2019) and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.
We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@dolphinics.com.
About us
Dolphin is a leader in PCI Express Software and Hardware for multi-computing systems.
Since 1992, Dolphin has developed multi-computing solutions for embedded, scientific, and OEM application.
Subscribe to our newsletter and stay up to date with the latest news and deals!
2019 © Dolphin ICS. ALL Rights Reserved.
